Guide to the Student Life Reference Collection, 1963-ongoing
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
Student Life Reference collection 1963-ongoing
University Archives, Duke University
Duke University. University Archives
0.5 Linear Feet approx. 400 Items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the University Archives to use this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Student Life Reference Collection was compiled from a variety of sources by University Archives for use in reference and research.
Collection Overview
Collection contains news clippings, flyers, brochures and other material pertaining to student life at Duke. Topics include health, sexuality, safety, and financial issues.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Duke University -- History -- 20th century
Duke University -- Students -- Social life and customs
Related Material
Freshman Life Reference Collection
Duke University Archives
Student Organizations Reference Collection
Duke University Archives
Contents of Collection
- Container List
  - AIDS, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Healthy Devils, circa 1985-
  - Measles, 1989-
  - Meningitis, 1987-
  - Safe rides/walks, 1985-
  - Sexuality, 1971-1990
  - Sexuality: P.I.S.C.E.S., circa 1976-1978
  - Student-faculty relations, 1982-
  - Student consumer programs, 1968-1971
  - Student [Health] Insurance Program, 1963-1980
  - Student life, clippings, circa 1974-
  - Student mental health services, 1973-1977
  - Students with disabilities, circa 1994-
  - Transfer students, 1982
  - Center for Counseling and Psychological Services (CAPS), (2 folders)
  - Testing Services Annual Report
  - Student Health